<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artifact on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/</link>
    <description>Recent content in artifact on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>cdn-migrate</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/cdn-migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/cdn-migrate/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl workflow artifact cdn-migrate Migrate artifact into CDN
Synopsis Migrate artifact from CDS to CDN cdsctl workflow artifact cdn-migrate &amp;lt;project_key&amp;gt; &amp;lt;workflow_name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;run_number&amp;gt;
CDN does not manage artifact with same name inside a run. They will be renamed _&amp;lt;artifact_name&amp;gt; Migrated artifacts will not be visible with cdsctl workflow result command
cdsctl workflow artifact cdn-migrate [ PROJECT-KEY WORKFLOW-NAME ] NUMBER Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>download</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/download/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl workflow artifact download Download artifacts of one Workflow Run
Synopsis Download artifacts of one Workflow Run
cdsctl workflow artifact download [ PROJECT-KEY WORKFLOW-NAME ] NUMBER [ARTIFACT-NAME] [flags] Options  --cdn-url string overwrite cdn url --exclude string exclude files from download - could be a regex: *.log Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/workflow/artifact/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl workflow artifact list List artifacts of one Workflow Run
Synopsis List artifacts of one Workflow Run
cdsctl workflow artifact list [ PROJECT-KEY WORKFLOW-NAME ] NUMBER [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
