<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design your Workflow on CDS Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design your Workflow on CDS Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Payload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/payload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/payload/</guid>
      <description>A CDS Workflow can be launched :
 manually, user can enter a Payload by webhooks / repository webhooks, payload contains the value sent by initiator of the hook scheduler, the payload contains the value of the default payload. You can edit the default payload on the root pipeline (on roadmap) listener, as a kafka listener. The payload will contain the content of the kafka message  A payload is a JSON value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Context</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/pipeline-context/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/pipeline-context/</guid>
      <description>After adding the pipeline, you can &amp;ldquo;Edit the pipeline Context&amp;rdquo; (sidebar).
Then, you can:
 add or remove application. Jobs can use cds.app.* configuration and or remove an environment. Jobs can use cds.env.* configuration enable / disable Pipeline Mutex  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run conditions on pipeline</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/run-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/run-conditions/</guid>
      <description>In CDS if you want to launch a pipeline in your workflow only in specific cases you can add conditions on your pipeline in your workflow. For example if you want to run this pipeline automatically only if the value of git.branch is master.
If you want to edit your pipeline condition on the user interface you have to select a node under edition mode of your workflow and click on Edit run conditons like this :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/join/</guid>
      <description>A join lets workflow to wait the end of two or more parent pipelines.
You can trigger one or many pipelines after a join.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutex</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/mutex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/mutex/</guid>
      <description>By default, the same pipeline can run at the same time on multiple runs.
In a CDS Workflow, you can limit running a pipeline one at a time.
Click on the pipeline → Edit the pipeline context → enable &amp;ldquo;Limit one run at run time&amp;rdquo;
Example of use case: run an integration test once on a particular environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidebar</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/sidebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/workflows/design/sidebar/</guid>
      <description>On the left sidebar, there is only one select box for filter on CDS Tags.
So, what&amp;rsquo;s a tag? A tag is a CDS Variable, exported as a tag. There are default tags as git.branch, git.hash, tiggered_by and environment. For example if you want to know on which branch the build was launched you just have to filter on a specific CDS tag (in this case git.branch)
Inside a job, a user can add a Tag with the worker command</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>