<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>features on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in features on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin features delete Delete
Synopsis Delete
cdsctl admin features delete NAME [flags] Options  --force Force delete without confirmation and exit 0 if resource does not exist Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl admin features	- Manage CDS feature flipping rules  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>export</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/export/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin features export Export a feature as a yaml file
Synopsis Export a feature as a yaml file
cdsctl admin features export NAME Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl admin features	- Manage CDS feature flipping rules  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>import</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/import/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/import/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin features import Import a feature as a yaml file
Synopsis Import a feature as a yaml file
cdsctl admin features import FILE Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl admin features	- Manage CDS feature flipping rules  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/features/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin features list List all the features
Synopsis List all the features
cdsctl admin features list [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key --verbose Display all object fields Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
