<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Actions on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Actions on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/artifact-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/artifact-download/</guid>
      <description>Artifact Download Action is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action can be used to retrieve an artifact previously uploaded by an Artifact Upload action.
Parameters  enabled: Enable artifact download path: Path where artifacts will be downloaded pattern: Empty: download all files. Otherwise, enter regexp pattern to choose file: (fileA|fileB) tag: Artifact are uploaded with a tag, generally {{.cds.version}}  Example  Workflow Configuration: a pipeline doing an upload artifact and another doing a download artifact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Upload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/artifact-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/artifact-upload/</guid>
      <description>Artifact Upload Action is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action can be used to upload artifacts in CDS. This is the recommended way to share files between pipelines or stages.
Parameters  path: Path of file to upload, example: ./src/yourFile.json tag: Artifact will be uploaded with a tag, generally {{.cds.version}}. enabled: Enable artifact upload, true or false destination: optional. Destination of this artifact. Use the name of integration attached on your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CheckoutApplication</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/checkoutapplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/checkoutapplication/</guid>
      <description>CheckoutApplication is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action clones a repository into a directory. If you want to clone a tag from your repository in this way, in your workflow payload you can add a key in your JSON like &amp;quot;git.tag&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;0.2&amp;quot;.
This will run git clone with the following options:
 --depth 50 --recursive authentication from Application VCS Strategy (ssh or http(s))  If you want to modify options depth or recursive, you have to use GitClone action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeployApplication</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/deployapplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/deployapplication/</guid>
      <description> DeployApplication is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action is useful only if you have a Deployment Plaftorm associated to your current application.
Example  Add a deployment platform on your application.   Create a workflow, add a pipeline and an application linked to a platform.   Or edit the pipeline context from your workflow view.   In the job, use action DeployApplication  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitClone</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/gitclone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/gitclone/</guid>
      <description>GitClone is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action clones a repository into a new directory.
Parameters  url - mandatory - the git URL must include information about the transport protocol, the address of the remote server, and the path to the repository. privateKey - optional - the private key to be able to git clone from ssh user - optional - the user to be able to git clone from https with authentication password - optional - the password to be able to git clone from https with authentication branch - optional - Instead of pointing the newly created HEAD to the branch pointed to by the cloned repository’s HEAD, point to {{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitTag</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/gittag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/gittag/</guid>
      <description>GitTag is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action creates a semver comptabible tag. You can use a pgp key to sign it.
Parameters  url - mandatory - URL must contain information about the transport protocol, the address of the remote server, and the path to the repository. authPrivateKey - optional - the private key to be able to git tag from ssh user - optional - the user to be able to git tag from https with authentication password - optional - the password to be able to git tag from https with authentication tagName - optional - Name of the tag you want to create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JUnit</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/junit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/junit/</guid>
      <description> JUnit is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action parses a given Junit formatted XML file to extract its test results.
Parameters  path: Path to a JUnit XML file  Example  Job Configuration.   Launch pipeline, check XUnit Result   And view details:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/release/</guid>
      <description> Release is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action creates a release on the git repository linked to the application, if repository manager implements it.
This is actually implemented for GitHub only.
Parameters  artifacts - optional - List of artifacts to upload, separated by &amp;lsquo;,&amp;rsquo;. You can also use regexp releaseNote - optional - release information tag - mandatory - Tag attached to the release title - mandatory - Set the title of the release  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Script</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/script/</guid>
      <description>Script is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action executes a given script with a given interpreter.
Parameters  script: Content of your script. You can put  #!/bin/bash  or
#!/bin/perl  at first line. This will define the interpreter.
Make sure that the binary used is in the pre-requisites of the action.
If you use a shebang bash, sh, zsh or ksh, CDS will return a failure on your step if an executed command fails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serve Static Files</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/serve-static-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/serve-static-files/</guid>
      <description>Serve Static Files Action is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action can be used to upload static files and serve them. For example your HTML report about coverage, tests, performances, &amp;hellip;
Pay attention this action is only available if your objectstore is configured to use Openstack Swift. And fow now by default your static files will be deleted after 2 months.
Parameters  name: Name to display in CDS UI and identify your static files path: Path where static files will be uploaded (example: mywebsite/*).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-docker-package</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-docker-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-docker-package/</guid>
      <description>Build image and push it to docker repository
Parameters  dockerOpts: Docker options, Enter &amp;ndash;no-cache &amp;ndash;pull if you want for example dockerRegistry: Docker Registry. Enter myregistry for build image myregistry/myimage:mytag dockerRegistryPassword: Docker Registry Password. Enter password to connect on your docker registry. dockerRegistryUsername: Docker Registry Username. Enter username to connect on your docker registry. dockerfileDirectory: Directory which contains your Dockerfile. imageName: Name of your docker image, without tag. Enter myimage for build image myregistry/myimage:mytag imageTag: Tag og your docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-go-build</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-go-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-go-build/</guid>
      <description>Go Build: compile a go program
Parameters  architecture: GOARCH artifactUpload: Upload Binary as CDS Artifact binary: Binary name: Put foo for go build -o foo cgoDisabled: detectRaceCondition: Enable data race detection. It&amp;rsquo;s flag -race flags: flags for go build. Put -ldflags &amp;ldquo;-X main.xyz=abc&amp;rdquo; for go build -ldflags &amp;ldquo;-X main.xyz=abc&amp;rdquo; os: GOOS package: go package to compile. Put host.ext/foo/bar for go build host.ext/foo/bar preRun: Pre-command. Example: export CGO_ENABLED=0 runGoGet: Run go get -u before go build  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash go: type: binary Value: go  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-nexus-upload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-nexus-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-nexus-upload/</guid>
      <description>Upload file on Nexus
Parameters  artifactId: Artifact id of the artifact extension: Extension of the artifact files: Regex of files you want to upload groupId: Group id of the artifact login: Login for nexus packaging: Packaging type of the artifact password: Password for nexus repository: Nexus repository that the artifact is contained in url: Nexus URL version: Version of the artifact. Supports resolving of &amp;lsquo;LATEST&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;RELEASE&amp;rsquo; and snapshot versions (&amp;lsquo;1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-perl-test</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-perl-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-perl-test/</guid>
      <description>Parameters  perllib: PERL_LIB, added to $PERL5LIB proveOptions: Options passed to prove testDirectory:  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash perl: type: binary Value: perl prove: type: binary Value: prove  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-publish-ovh-metrics</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-publish-ovh-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-publish-ovh-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Publish a metric on OVH Metrics. See https://www.ovh.com/fr/data-platforms/metrics/ and doc on https://docs.ovh.com/gb/en/cloud/metrics/
Parameters  file: Metrics file to push (optional) See: http://www.warp10.io/apis/ingress/ labels: Labels of your metric (one K/V per line separated by a space) name: Name of you metric (optional) region: Metrics region token: Metrics write token value: Value of your metric (T=true) See: http://www.warp10.io/apis/ingress/  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash curl: type: binary Value: curl  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-python-pylint</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-python-pylint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-python-pylint/</guid>
      <description>Run pylint. By default, each pylint recommendation will be displayed as a Junit test. The short errors are fully contained inside the test title, an arrow (-&amp;gt;) will be present if a part of the recommendation is displayed in the test body.
Parameters  extra_options: Extra options to pass during pylint invocation. ignore: List of ignored files / directory (base name, not path), separated by a ; module_path: List of modules paths (absolute or relative) to launch pylint into, separated by a ;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-sonar-scanner</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-sonar-scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-sonar-scanner/</guid>
      <description>Run Sonar analysis. You must have a file sonar-project.properties in your source directory.
Parameters  sonar-project.properties: sonar-project.properties file sonarBranch: The Sonar branch (e.g. master) sonarDownloadURL: The download URL of Sonar CLI sonarPassword: The Sonar server&amp;rsquo;s password sonarURL: The URL of the Sonar server sonarUsername: The Sonar server&amp;rsquo;s username sonarVersion: SonarScanner&amp;rsquo;s version to use workspace: The directory where your project is (e.g. /go/src/github.com/ovh/cds)  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash plugin-archive: type: plugin Value: plugin-archive plugin-download: type: plugin Value: plugin-download  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-split-download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-split-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-split-download/</guid>
      <description>Download Artifacts which were uploaded using CDS_SplitUploadArtifact action.
Parameters  destinationFile: Destination File to save the file. (Mandatory). (like dist.tar.gz) pattern: Prefix pattern to identify files to be downloaded. (Mandatory). (like bigfile-*) prefixHandle: Prefix of the Artifacts uploaded. (Mandatory). tag: Tag to identify uploaded artifacts. Default tag value is CDS run version number. (Optional)  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-split-upload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-split-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/cds-split-upload/</guid>
      <description>Split and Upload Artifact with size greater than 500 MB.
Parameters  numericSuffixes: Use numeric suffixes instead of alphabetic. Default suffix is set to be Numeric. (Optional) prefixHandle: Prefix to be added to destination files after split. (Mandatory) sourceFile: Artifact File to be split and uploaded. (Mandatory). splitSize: Size of each split files. Default size is 200MB. (Optional) tag: Tag to identify uploaded artifacts. Default tag value is CDS run version number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-archive</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-archive/</guid>
      <description> This is a plugin to compress or uncompress an archive. Supported formats: .zip, .tar, .tar.gz, .tar.bz2, .tar.xz, .tar.lz4, .tar.sz, and .rar (extract-only)
Parameters  action: &amp;ldquo;compress&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;uncompress&amp;rdquo; an archive destination: The destination path source: The source path  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-clair</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-clair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-clair/</guid>
      <description> This is a plugin to run clair analysis
Parameters  image: Image to analyze  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-download/</guid>
      <description> This is a plugin to download file from URL
Parameters  filepath: The destination of your file to be copied headers: Specific headers to add to your request (&amp;ldquo;headerName&amp;rdquo;=&amp;ldquo;value&amp;rdquo; newline separated list) url: The url of your file  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-group-tmpl</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-group-tmpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-group-tmpl/</guid>
      <description> This actions helps you generate a marathon group application file. It takes a config template file as a single application, and creates the group with the variables specified for each application in the applications files. Check documentation on text/template for more information https://golang.org/pkg/text/template.
Parameters  applications: Applications file variables config: Template file to use output: Output path for generated file (default to .out or just trimming .tpl extension)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-kafka-publish</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-kafka-publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-kafka-publish/</guid>
      <description>This action helps you to send data through Kafka across every network.
You are able to send a custom &amp;ldquo;message&amp;rdquo; file and all the artifacts you want: there is no file size limit. To improve security, you can encrypt the files content with a GPG Key. From the consumer side, you will need to decrypt files content with you GPG private key and your passphrase.
This action is a CDS Plugin packaged as a single binary file you can download and use to listen and consume data coming from CDS through Kafka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-marathon</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-marathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-marathon/</guid>
      <description>This action helps you to deploy on Mesos/Marathon. Provide a marathon.json file to configure deployment.
Your marathon.json file can be templated with cds variables &amp;ldquo;{{.cds.variables}}&amp;rdquo;. Enable &amp;ldquo;waitForDeployment&amp;rdquo; option to ensure deployment is successful.
Parameters  configuration: Marathon application configuration file (json format) insecureSkipVerify: Skip SSL Verify if you want to use self-signed certificate password: Marathon Password (please use project, application or environment variables) timeout: Marathon deployment timeout (seconds). Used only if &amp;ldquo;waitForDeployment&amp;rdquo; is true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-npm-audit-parser</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-npm-audit-parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-npm-audit-parser/</guid>
      <description> This is a plugin to parse npm audit report
Parameters  file: Path to audit file (generally generated by npm audit &amp;ndash;json &amp;gt;{{.cds.workspace}}/audit.json for example)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-ssh-cmd</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-ssh-cmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-ssh-cmd/</guid>
      <description> This plugin helps you to run cmd on remote server over ssh.
Parameters  command: Command commandTimeout: Command Timeout (seconds) hostnames: Hostnames (comma separated values) privateKey: SSH RSA private key timeout: Timeout (seconds) username: Username  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-tmpl</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-tmpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-tmpl/</guid>
      <description> This action helps you generates a file using a template file and text/template golang package.
Check documentation on text/template for more information https://golang.org/pkg/text/template.
Parameters  file: Template file to use output: Output path for generated file (default to .out or just trimming .tpl extension) params: Parameters to pass on the template file (key=value newline separated list)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-venom</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-venom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/actions/plugin-venom/</guid>
      <description>This plugin helps you to run venom. Venom: https://github.com/ovh/venom.
Add an extra step of type junit on your job to view tests results on CDS UI.
Parameters  exclude: Exclude some files, one file per line loglevel: Log Level: debug, info, warn or error output: Directory where output xunit result file parallel: Launch Test Suites in parallel. Enter here number of routines path: Path containers yml venom files. Format: adirectory/, .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>