<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CDS Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CDS Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Actions</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin/</guid>
      <description>Built-in actions are integred in CDS. You can’t modify it.
Built-in actions :
Artifact Download Artifact Upload GitClone JUnit Script </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate a Token</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.token/</guid>
      <description> Purpose In order to start a worker or a Hatchery, you need to provide a token to be able to register on CDS API.
CLI Run the following command, replace yourgroup with your group
$ cds generate token -g yourgroup -e persistent  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.github/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on Github Create a CDS application on Github Go to https://github.com/settings/developers and Register a new application: set an application name, the url and a description. Authorization callback URL: http(s)://&amp;lt;your-cds-api&amp;gt;/repositories_manager/oauth2/callback
On the next page Github give you a Client ID and a Client Secret
Connect CDS To Github Set env CDS_VCS_REPOSITORIES_GITHUB_CLIENTSECRET or update your configuration file with &amp;lt;client-secret&amp;gt;:
[vcs.repositories.github] clientsecret = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;client-secret&amp;gt;&amp;quot;  Then restart CDS
With CDS CLI run :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction/</guid>
      <description>What is CDS? Enterprise-Grade Continuous Delivery &amp;amp; DevOps Automation Open Source Platform
 Easy to deploy Cloud native Scalable &amp;amp; Extensible Infrastructure &amp;amp; Architecture agnostic Event-Driven Pipeline  Designed for scalability, CDS tasks can run either on cloud infrastructure or on your own machines, should you start some workers using a hatchery.
CDS exposes an API available to workers and humans through CLI or WebUI.
What does CDS do? Basically, CDS allows users to create building and delivery pipelines for all your applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.pipeline/</guid>
      <description>A pipeline describes how things need to be executed in order to achieve wanted result. In CDS, a pipeline a defined on a project and can be used on several applications inside the same project.
A pipeline is structured in sequential stages containing one or multiple concurrent jobs.
In CDS there is several types of pipeline : build, testing and deployment. In Pipeline configuration file, default type is build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requirements</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.requirements/</guid>
      <description>CDS API is the core component of CDS. To start CDS api, the only mandatory dependency is a PostgreSQL database and a path to the directory containing other CDS binaries.
There is are two ways to set up CDS:
 as toml configuration over environment variables.  CDS API Third-parties At the minimum, CDS needs a PostgreSQL Database &amp;gt;= 9.4 and Redis &amp;gt;= 3.2. But for serious usage your may need :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Actions</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user-actions/</guid>
      <description>CDS User Actions are developed in CDS. There are available on all CDS Installation. They use built-in action(s) and / or other existing action(s).
There can be created by CLI and / or Web UI.
User actions from CDS Contributions :
cds-docker-package cds-go-build cds-nexus-upload cds-perl-test cds-publish-ovh-metrics </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker Setup</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-setup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Why would you need to setup your own worker ? There is several cases where one would need to setup his own worker:
 Perform incremental build Build on a specific architecture Perform integration tests in a specific network  How does this work ? Workers authenticate on CDS with a token and have the same permissions as the user who generated it.
Bottom line, if you can access the application, your worker will too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write your own hatchery</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.hatchery-create/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.hatchery-create/</guid>
      <description>Example with a creation of a VSphere hatchery  First of all you need to create a new package like the other into the hatchery package. Let&amp;rsquo;s call this package vsphere for our example.
 You have to implement the Service interface (see here) in order to configure launch this new hatchery mode via CDS engine CLI.
 Your have to create a Configuration structure composed of the hatchery.CommonConfiguration and the variables you need to access to Vsphere API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.bitbucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.bitbucket/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on your Bitbucket instance You need to perform the following steps :
 Bitbucket admin privileges A RSA Key Pair  Create a CDS application in BitBucket In Bitbucket go to Administration Settings / Application Links. Create a new Application with :
 Name : CDS Type : Generic Application Application URL : Your CDS URL Display URL : Your CDS URL  On this application, you just have to set up OAuth Incoming Authentication :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepts</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts/</guid>
      <description>Project A project contains applications, pipelines and environments.
A project is the first level of permissions management. Any CDS application has to be created inside a project.
The project key has to be unique among all projects in CDS.
At creation, a project has to have at least one group with edition permissions on it. It is possible to use either an existing group or create a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.download/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll find last release of CDS on Github Releases</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Pipeline with CLI</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.first-pipeline-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.first-pipeline-cli/</guid>
      <description>Create a project The first step is to create your own Project. A project contains applications, pipelines and environments.
You can use either the CLI or the UI to create your project.
$ cds project add TEST &amp;quot;My test project&amp;quot; test-team OK  Create a simple pipeline $ cds pipeline add TEST hello-pip Pipeline hello-pip created.  Create an application $ cds application add TEST hello-world Aplication hello-world created.  Configure your pipeline We will add a script action in pipeline saying &amp;ldquo;Hello World !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/getting-started/getting-started.first-pipeline-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/getting-started/getting-started.first-pipeline-ui/</guid>
      <description> 0 - Prerequisite You must have a CDS Running. See Installation for more information.
1 - Create Project 2 - Create Application 3 - Create Pipeline 4 - Create Stage and Job 5 - Run Pipeline  Click on &amp;ldquo;Play button&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gitlab</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.gitlab/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on your Gitlab instance What you need to perform the following steps :
 Gitlab admin privileges  Create a CDS application on Gitlab In Gitlab go to Settings / Application section. Create a new application with :
 Name : CDS Redirect URI : http(s):///repositories_manager/oauth2/callback  Scopes :
 API read_user read_registry  Connect CDS to Gitlab Using CDS CLI, run :
 $ cds admin reposmanager add GITLAB mygitlab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatcheries</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries/</guid>
      <description>Hatchery is a service dedicated to spawn and kill worker in accordance with build queue needs.
An hatchery is started with permissions to build all pipelines accessible from a given group, using token.
There are 6 modes for hatcheries:
 Local (Start local workers on a single host) Marathon (Start worker model instances on a mesos cluster with marathon framework) Swarm (Start worker on a docker swarm cluster) Openstack (Start virtual machines on an openstack cluster) VSphere (Start virtual machines on an VSphere cluster)  Local mode Hatchery starts workers directly as local process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Swarm</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.swarm/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using Docker Swarm to spawn CDS Worker.
Start Swarm hatchery Generate a token for group:
$ cds generate token -g shared.infra -e persistent fc300aad48242d19e782a37d361dfa3e55868a629e52d7f6825c7ce65a72bf92  Edit the CDS configuration or set the dedicated environment variables. To enable the hactchery, just set the API HTTP and GRPC URL, the token freshly generated.
This hatchery use the standard docker environment variables to connect to a docker host.
Then start hatchery:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plugins Actions</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins/</guid>
      <description>CDS Plugin System lets users develop complex actions. See How to write a plugin
CDS Administrators have to import plugins on CDS to let user use them.
Plugins from CDS Contributions:
plugin-download plugin-group-tmpl plugin-kafka-publish plugin-marathon plugin-ssh-cmd plugin-tmpl plugin-venom </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Worker Model From Docker Hub</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-docker-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-docker-simple/</guid>
      <description>A worker model of type docker can be spawned by a Hatchery Docker Swarm.
Register a worker Model from an existing Docker Image Docker Image golang:1.8.1 have a &amp;ldquo;curl&amp;rdquo; in $PATH, so it can be used as it is.
 In the UI, click on the wheel on the hand right top corner and select *workers&amp;rdquo; (or go the the route #/worker) At the bottom of the page, fill the form  Name of your worker Golang-1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker/</guid>
      <description>A pipeline is structured in sequential stages containing one or multiple concurrent jobs. A Job will be executed by a worker.
Building your own worker model enables you to integrate your own tools, or to customize the tools you need to use. For instance, to build an AngularJs application, you shall need a worker capable of installing npm tools, importing bower packages (these are nodeJs tools), building webfonts with fontforge&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker Model</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.model/</guid>
      <description>Purpose The goal of CDS is to start a worker when you need it, which should match all your requirements exactly. In order to scale automatically on demand, it is possible to register a worker model.
The goal of a worker model is to describe the capabilities of a given docker/iso image in terms of architecture, pre-installed binaries or libraries.
Types There are 2 types of worker models:
 Docker images, see how to create a worker model docker Openstack images, see how to create a worker model openstack  Capabilities Capabilities have a name, a type and a value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines/</guid>
      <description> First Pipeline with CLI Use Configuration File Actions Templates Variables Job&amp;#39;s Requirements  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.configuration/</guid>
      <description>The toml configuration can be provided by a file, via consul k/v store or via vault.
Start CDS with local configuration file You can also generate a configuration file template with the following command.
$ $PATH_TO_CDS/engine config new &amp;gt; my_conf_file.toml  Edit this file.
Check your configuration file with
$ $PATH_TO_CDS/engine config check my_conf_file.toml Reading configuration file my_new_file.toml Configuration file OK  Run CDS
$ $PATH_TO_CDS/engine start api --config my_conf_file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Openstack</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.openstack/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using Openstack infrastructure to spawn each CDS Workers inside dedicated virtual machine.
Start Opentack hatchery Generate a token for group:
$ cds generate token -g shared.infra -e persistent fc300aad48242d19e782a37d361dfa3e55868a629e52d7f6825c7ce65a72bf92  Edit the CDS configuration or set the dedicated environment variables. To enable the hactchery, just set the API HTTP and GRPC URL, the token freshly generated and the openstack variables.
Then start hatchery:
engine start hatchery:openstack --config config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Vsphere</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.vsphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.vsphere/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using VMWare Vsphere infrastructure to spawn each CDS Workers inside dedicated VM.
Pre-requisites This hatchery spawns VM which obtains IP from DHCP. So first you have to create a DHCP server on your host with NAT if you want to access to the internet. In order to create you have multiple possibilities like create your own VM with a DHCP server configured or if you are comfortable with the VMWare tools you can use the NSX system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.job/</guid>
      <description>The Job is more important concept in CDS. It will be composed of steps which will be run sequencially. A Job will be executed is a dedicated workspace and each new run of a job will have a new dedicated workspace. It means that you cannot share a workspace between jobs or between two runs of a job.
A Job will be executed by a worker. CDS will choose and provision a worker for dependending of the Requirements you define on your job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repositories Manager</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager/</guid>
      <description>CDS can be linked to following repositories manager :
 Atlassian Stash / Bitbucket Github Gitlab  It allows you to enable some CDS features such as :
 Create application in CDS from Bitbucket or Github Attach an application to its Bitbucket or Github repository Fully automatic hook management Branch filtering on application workflows Commit logs on pipeline build details  Go through this tutorial to enable the link between repositories managers and CDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Docker Worker Model with your own image</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-docker-customized/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-docker-customized/</guid>
      <description>A worker model of type docker can be spawned by a Hatchery Docker Swarm
Setup Docker Worker Model with your own image In this example, we will build a Docker model able to build an AngularJs application with webfonts. To create webfonts, a grunt task (optionnally) requires fontforge and ttfautohint.
The following tools must be included in the model:
 NodeJs and npm bower grunt-cli gulp-cli fontforge ttfautohint  We will use the official nodejs image from Docker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Configuration File</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.configuration-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.configuration-file/</guid>
      <description>You can define a pipeline both in json format or in yaml format. Default is yaml format.
Basic configuration If you have a pretty simple build pipeline with one stage and one job. You can write such a configuration file
steps: - script: echo I&#39;m the firt step - script: echo I&#39;m the second step  This defines a pipeline of type build (it&amp;rsquo;s the default type), named Build (the default name for a build Pipeline).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actions</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions/</guid>
      <description>Inside a Job, each steps is based on an action.
Types of actions :
 Built-in actions, available on each CDS Installation User actions, added by CDS Administrators for now Plugins actions, added by CDS Administrators  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Database Management</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.database/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.database/</guid>
      <description>CDS provides all needed tools scripts to perform Schema creation and auto-migration. Those tools are embedded inside the engine binary.
The migration files are available to download on Github Releases and the archive is named sql.tar.gz. You have to download it and untar (tar xvzf sql.tar.gz).
Creation On a brand new database run the following command:
$ $PATH_TO_CDS/engine database upgrade --db-host &amp;lt;host&amp;gt; --db-port &amp;lt;port&amp;gt; --db-user &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; --db-password &amp;lt;password&amp;gt; --db-name &amp;lt;database&amp;gt; --migrate-dir $PATH_TO_CDS/engine/sql --limit 0  Upgrade On an existing database, run the following command on each CDS update:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation/</guid>
      <description> Requirements Download Configuration Database Management Ready to RUN Advanced Startup  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Openstack Worker Model</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-openstack/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using OVH.com Openstack infrastructure
Create Openstack user In OVH manager, in cloud section, click on the menu on the Servers&amp;gt;Openstack item.
You will be able to create a worker model Openstack user, enter description (name and password will be generated).
Add Openstack worker model We need to define an Openstack worker model to have Openstack hatchery booting workers.
We will create a model called docker:
 With low hardware capacity (vps-ssd-1) On Debian 8 With docker ready to use Git installed  First, define a udata file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup VSphere Worker Model</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-vsphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.worker-model-vsphere/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using VSphere infrastructure
Add VSphere worker model We need to define a VSphere worker model to have VSphere hatchery booting workers.
We will create a worker model called debian8-docker:
 On Debian 8 With docker ready to use Git installed  First, define a udata file. It is a shell script executed just after the boot sequence complete. Our udata will look like this:
# Install docker cd $HOME apt-get -y --force-yes update &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /tmp/user_data 2&amp;gt;&amp;amp;1 apt-get install -y --force-yes apt-transport-https ca-certificates &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /tmp/user_data 2&amp;gt;&amp;amp;1 apt-key adv --keyserver hkp://p80.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.step/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.step/</guid>
      <description>The steps of a job is the list of the different operation performed by the CDS worker. Each step is based on an Action which is defined by CDS. The list of all actions is defined on *&amp;lt;your cds url ui&amp;gt;/#/action*. On the very first step failed, the job is marked as Failed and execution is stopped.
You can define a Step as final. It mean that even if the job is failed, the step will be executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Templates</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates/</guid>
      <description>CDS models allow users to:
 quickly create a workflow, with applications, pipelines and triggers reuse best practices for some use cases  Templates from CDS Contributions :
cds-template-cds-plugin cds-template-cds-template cds-template-deploy-marathon-app cds-template-only-git-clone-job cds-template-plain </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write a Plugin</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.write-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.write-plugin/</guid>
      <description>A CDS worker executes job, and job is composed of steps.
A step is :
 a builtin action, as GitClone, etc&amp;hellip; read more a user action read more a Plugin Action  A Plugin is a Golang Binary.
Take a look at https://github.com/ovh/cds/tree/master/sdk/plugin/dummy/dummy_plugin.go
Contribute on https://github.com/ovh/cds/tree/master/contrib/plugins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write your own hatchery</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.write.hatchery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.write.hatchery/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contribute to add new Hatchery mode.
See Tutorial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready to RUN</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.ready-to-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.ready-to-run/</guid>
      <description> Docker Compose  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Requirement Nginx</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.service-link-requirement-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.service-link-requirement-nginx/</guid>
      <description>Add the service requirement  Name: mypg. This will be the service hostname Type: service Value: nginx:1.11.1. This is the name of docker image to link to current job  And a requirement model which allow you to execute apt-get install -y postgresql-client
worker-model-docker-simple.md
Add a step of type script docker image nginx:1.11.1 start a nginx at startup. So, it&amp;rsquo;s now available on http://mynginx
curl -v -X GET http://mynginx  Execute Pipeline</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variables</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.variables/</guid>
      <description>In CDS, it is possible to define variables at different levels:
 Project Environment Application  Variable types Existing variable types:
 String Text Boolean Number Password Key  Placeholder format All variables in CDS can be invoked using the simple {{.VAR}} format. To simplify the use between all the variable sources, we have defined the following prefixes:
 Action variable: {{.VAR}} Builtin CDS: {{.cds.VAR}} Git: {{.git.VAR}} Pipeline: {{.cds.pip.VAR}} Application: {{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced/</guid>
      <description> Generate a Token Hatcheries Worker Repositories Manager Write a Plugin  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Startup</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.advanced/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This section will help you to undestand how to start all the differents components of CDS: UI, API and the other µServices.
Pre-requisites You need :
 to download the latest release a properly formatted configuration file, a properly configured database, the desired third-parties up and running.  Engine startup The CDS engine is made of following components:
 API Hatcheries (local, docker, openstack, swarm, vshpere) Hooks  To start a services you just have to run $PATH_TO_CDS/engine start &amp;lt;service&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job&#39;s Requirements</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.requirements/</guid>
      <description>Type of requirements:
 Binary Model Hostname Network Service Memory OS (Not yet implemented) Architecture (Not yet implemented)  A Job will be executed by a worker.
CDS will choose and provision a worker for dependending of the requirements you define on your job.
You can set as many requirements as you want, following those rules :
 Only one model can be set as requirement Only one hostname can be set as requirement Memory and Services requirements are availabe only on Docker models  Screenshot Here a job with two requirements, Memory and Model:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Requirement PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.service-link-requirement-pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.service-link-requirement-pg/</guid>
      <description>Add the service requirement Requirement Service
 Name: mypg. This will be the service hostname Type: service Value: postgres:9.5.3 POSTGRES_USER=myuser POSTGRES_PASSWORD=mypassword. This is the name of docker image to link to current job  And a requirement model which allow you to execute apt-get install -y postgresql-client, see HowTo
Add a step of type script docker image postgres:9.5.3 start a postgresql at startup. So, it&amp;rsquo;s now available on mypg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track CDS Pipeline from Git command line </title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.cds-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials.cds-track/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial introduce the cds track &amp;lt;git commit&amp;gt; function of CDS cli.
Goal: Immediate feedback cds track aims to display in your terminal the status of the pipeline building code refered by given commit hash.
Push your branch, start cds track and get immediate feedback.
Git track will display all pipelines related to given hash.
This means triggered testing and deployment pipelines will be displayed.
Git alias sugar To enhance even more your daily routine, you can create a git alias:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/tutorials/tutorials/</guid>
      <description> Worker Setup Write your own hatchery Setup Worker Model From Docker Hub Setup Docker Worker Model with your own image Setup Openstack Worker Model Setup VSphere Worker Model Service Requirement Nginx Service Requirement PostgreSQL Track CDS Pipeline from Git command line   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.artifact-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.artifact-download/</guid>
      <description>Artifact Download Action is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action can be used to get artifact uploaded by the Artifact Upload action
Action Parameter  application: Application from where artifacts will be downloaded pipeline: Pipeline from where artifacts will be downloaded tag: Tag set in the Artifact Upload action path: Path where artifacts will be downloaded  Example  Workflow Configuration: a pipeline doing an upload artifact and another doing a download artifact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Upload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.artifact-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.artifact-upload/</guid>
      <description> Artifact Upload Action is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action can be used to upload artifact in CDS. This is the good way to share files between pipelines or stages.
Action Parameter  path: Path of file to upload tag: Tag to apply to your file.  Example  Create a file myFile and upload it.   Launch pipeline, check logs   View artifact  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.ready-to-run.docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/installation/installation.ready-to-run.docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>Run with Docker-Compose The docker-compose.yml contains:
 cds-db service with a postgresql cds-cache service with a redis cds-migrate service to prepare DB tables cds-api service cds-ui service cds-hatchery-swarm service cds-hatchery-local service  Docker compose is very convenient to launch CDS for testing it. But this is not recommended for a Production Installation.
How to run $ git clone https://github.com/ovh/cds.git $ cd cds $ export HOSTNAME=$(hostname) # Create PG Database $ docker-compose up --no-recreate -d cds-db # check if db is UP # check if last log is &amp;quot;LOG: database system is ready to accept connections&amp;quot; $ docker-compose logs $ docker-compose up --no-recreate cds-migrate # You should have this log: &amp;quot;cds_cds-migrate_1 exited with code 0&amp;quot; # run API and UI $ docker-compose up cds-api cds-ui  Open a browser on http://localhost:2015, then register a new user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitClone</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.gitclone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.gitclone/</guid>
      <description>GitClone is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action clone a repository into a new directory.
Git Clone will be done with a depth of 1.
You can use a privateKey, this is usually a project or application variable of type key. {{.cds.app.a-key.pub}}
Parameters  url - mandatory - URL must contain information about the transport protocol, the address of the remote server, and the path to the repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JUnit</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.junit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.junit/</guid>
      <description> JUnit is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action parse given file to extract Unit Test results.
Parameters  path: Path to junit xml file  Example  Job Configuration.   Launch pipeline, check XUnit Result   And view details:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Script</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.builtin.script/</guid>
      <description>Script is a builtin action, you can&amp;rsquo;t modify it.
This action execute a script, written in script attribute
Parameters  script: Content of your script. You can put  #!/bin/bash  or
#!/bin/perl  at first line.
Make sure that the binary used is in the pre-requisites of action.
If you use a shebang bash, sh, zsh or ksh, CDS will return a failure on your step if an executed command fails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stage</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/introduction/introduction.concepts.stage/</guid>
      <description>Usually in CDS a build pipeline is structured of the following stages :
 Compile stage : Build the binaries Analysis &amp;amp; Unit Tests stage : Run all unit tests and analyse code quality Packaging stage : Build the final package, Virtual Machine Image or Docker Image.  In CDS, stages are executed sequentially if the previous stage is successfull.
You can define trigger conditions on a stage, to enable it on certain conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-docker-package</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-docker-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-docker-package/</guid>
      <description>Build image and push it to docker repository
Parameters  dockerOpts: Docker options, Enter &amp;ndash;no-cache &amp;ndash;pull if you want for example dockerRegistry: Docker Registry. Enter myregistry for build image myregistry/myimage:mytag dockerfileDirectory: Directory which contains your Dockerfile. imageName: Name of your docker image, without tag. Enter myimage for build image myregistry/myimage:mytag imageTag: Tag of your docker image. Enter mytag for build image myregistry/myimage:mytag. {{.cds.version}} is a good tag from CDS. You can use many tags: firstTag,SecondTag Example : {{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-go-build</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-go-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-go-build/</guid>
      <description>Go Build: compile a go program
Parameters  architecture: GOOS artifactUpload: Upload Binary as CDS Artifact binary: Binary name: Put foo for go build -o foo cgoDisabled: if true (checked) -&amp;gt; export CGO_ENABLED=0 before go build detectRaceCondition: Enable data race detection. It&amp;rsquo;s flag -race flags: flags for go build. Put -ldflags &amp;ldquo;-X main.xyz=abc&amp;rdquo; for go build -ldflags &amp;ldquo;-X main.xyz=abc&amp;rdquo; gopath: set a $GOPATH. If empty, this action try to get env $GOPATH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-nexus-upload</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-nexus-upload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-nexus-upload/</guid>
      <description>Upload file on Nexus
Parameters  artifactId: Artifact id of the artifact extension: Extension of the artifact files: Regex of files you want to upload groupId: Group id of the artifact login: Login for nexus packaging: Packaging type of the artifact password: Password for nexus repository: Nexus repository that the artifact is contained in url: Nexus URL version: Version of the artifact. Supports resolving of &amp;lsquo;LATEST&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;RELEASE&amp;rsquo; and snapshot versions (&amp;lsquo;1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-perl-test</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-perl-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-perl-test/</guid>
      <description>Test with prove on perl source code
Parameters  proveOptions: Options passed to prove testDirectory: Directory in which prove will be launched  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash perl: type: binary Value: perl prove: type: binary Value: prove  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-publish-ovh-metrics</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-publish-ovh-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.user.cds-publish-ovh-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Publish a metric on OVH Metrics. See https://www.ovh.com/fr/data-platforms/metrics/ and doc on https://docs.ovh.com/gb/en/cloud/metrics/
Parameters  file: Metrics file to push (optional) See: http://www.warp10.io/apis/ingress/ labels: Labels of your metric (one K/V per line separated by a space) name: Name of you metric (optional) region: Metrics region token: Metrics write token value: Value of your metric (T=true) See: http://www.warp10.io/apis/ingress/  Requirements  bash: type: binary Value: bash curl: type: binary Value: curl  More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-template-cds-plugin</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-cds-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-cds-plugin/</guid>
      <description>This template creates a pipeline for building CDS Plugin with:
 A &amp;ldquo;Commit Stage&amp;rdquo; with one job &amp;ldquo;Compile&amp;rdquo; Job contains two steps: GitClone and CDS_GoBuild  Parameters  package.root: example: github.com/ovh/cds package.sub: Directory inside your repository where is the plugin. Enter &amp;ldquo;contrib/plugins/your-plugin&amp;rdquo; for github.com/ovh/cds/contrib/plugins/your-plugin
 repo: Your source code repository
  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-template-cds-template</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-cds-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-cds-template/</guid>
      <description>This template creates a pipeline for building CDS Template with:
 A &amp;ldquo;Commit Stage&amp;rdquo; with one job &amp;ldquo;Compile&amp;rdquo; Job contains two steps: GitClone and CDS_GoBuild  Parameters  package.root: example: github.com/ovh/cds package.sub: Directory inside your repository where is the template. Enter &amp;ldquo;contrib/templates/your-plugin&amp;rdquo; for github.com/ovh/cds/contrib/templates/your-plugin
 repo: Your source code repository
  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-template-deploy-marathon-app</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-deploy-marathon-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-deploy-marathon-app/</guid>
      <description>This template creates:
 a deployment pipeline with one stage, and containing one job job calls plugin-marathon an application with a variable named &amp;ldquo;marathon.config&amp;rdquo; uses environment variables marathonHost, password and user  Please update Application / Environment Variables after creating application.
Parameters  docker.image: Your docker image without the tag marathon.appID: Your marathon application ID marathon.config: Content of your marathon.json file  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-template-only-git-clone-job</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-only-git-clone-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-only-git-clone-job/</guid>
      <description>This template creates:
 a build pipeline with one stage, containing one job job contains 2 steps: GitClone and a empty script.  Pipeline name contains Application name. If you want to make a reusable pipeline, please consider updating this name after creating application.
Parameters  repo: Your source code repository  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cds-template-plain</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-plain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.templates.cds-template-plain/</guid>
      <description>This template creates:
 a build pipeline with two stages: Commit Stage and Packaging Stage a deploy pipeline with one stage: Deploy Stage  Commit Stage:
 run git clone run make build  Packaging Stage:
 run docker build and docker push  Deploy Stage:
 it&amp;rsquo;s an empty script  Packaging and Deploy are optional.
Parameters  repo: Your source code repository withDeploy: Do you want an deploy Pipeline?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>header</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/_header/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-download</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-download/</guid>
      <description>This is a plugin to download file from URL
Parameters  filepath: the destination of your file to be copied headers: specific headers to add to your request (&amp;ldquo;headerName&amp;rdquo;=&amp;ldquo;value&amp;rdquo; newline separated list) url: the url of your file  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-group-tmpl</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-group-tmpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-group-tmpl/</guid>
      <description>This actions helps you generate a marathon group application file. It takes a config template file as a single application, and creates the group with the variables specified for each application in the applications files. Check documentation on text/template for more information https://golang.org/pkg/text/template.
Parameters  applications: Applications file variables config: Template file to use output: Output path for generated file (default to .out or just trimming .tpl extension)  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-kafka-publish</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-kafka-publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-kafka-publish/</guid>
      <description>This action helps you to send data through Kafka across every network.
You are able to send a custom &amp;quot;message&amp;quot; file and all the artifacts you want: there is no file size limit. To improve security, you can encrypt the files content with a GPG Key. From the consumer side, you will need to decrypt files content with you GPG private key and your passphrase. This action is a CDS Plugin packaged as a single binary file you can download and use to listen and consume data coming from CDS through Kafka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-marathon</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-marathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-marathon/</guid>
      <description>This action helps you to deploy on Mesos/Marathon. Provide a marathon.json file to configure deployment.
Your marathon.json file can be templated with cds variables &amp;ldquo;{{.cds.variables}}&amp;rdquo;. Enable &amp;ldquo;waitForDeployment&amp;rdquo; option to ensure deployment is successfull.
Parameters  configuration: Marathon application configuration file (json format) insecureSkipVerify: Skip SSL Verify if you want to use self-signed certificate password: Marathon Password (please use project, application or environment variables) timeout: Marathon deployment timeout (seconds). Used only if &amp;ldquo;waitForDeployment&amp;rdquo; is true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-ssh-cmd</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-ssh-cmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-ssh-cmd/</guid>
      <description>This plugin helps you to run cmd on remote server over ssh.
Parameters  command: Command commandTimeout: Command Timeout (seconds) hostnames: Hostnames (comma separated values) privateKey: SSH RSA private key timeout: Timeout (seconds) username: Username  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-tmpl</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-tmpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-tmpl/</guid>
      <description>This action helps you generates a file using a template file and text/template golang package.
Check documentation on text/template for more information https://golang.org/pkg/text/template.
Parameters  file: Template file to use output: Output path for generated file (default to .out or just trimming .tpl extension) params: Parameters to pass on the template file (key=value newline separated list)  More More documentation on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plugin-venom</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-venom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/building-pipelines/building-pipelines.actions.plugins.plugin-venom/</guid>
      <description>This plugin helps you to run venom. Venom: https://github.com/ovh/venom.
Add an extra step of type junit on your job to view tests results on CDS UI.
Parameters  details: Output Details Level: low, medium, high exclude: Exclude some files, one file per line loglevel: Log Level: debug, info, warn or error output: Directory where output xunit result file parallel: Launch Test Suites in parallel. Enter here number of routines path: Path containers yml venom files.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>