<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanceds on CDS Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advanceds on CDS Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate a Token</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.token/</guid>
      <description> Purpose In order to start a worker or a Hatchery, you need to provide a token to be able to register on CDS API.
CLI Run the following command, replace yourgroup with your group
$ cds generate token -g yourgroup -e persistent  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.github/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on Github Create a CDS application on Github Go to https://github.com/settings/developers and Register a new application: set an application name, the url and a description. Authorization callback URL: http(s)://&amp;lt;your-cds-api&amp;gt;/repositories_manager/oauth2/callback
On the next page Github give you a Client ID and a Client Secret
Connect CDS To Github Set env CDS_VCS_REPOSITORIES_GITHUB_CLIENTSECRET or update your configuration file with &amp;lt;client-secret&amp;gt;:
[vcs.repositories.github] clientsecret = &amp;quot;&amp;lt;client-secret&amp;gt;&amp;quot;  Then restart CDS
With CDS CLI run :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.bitbucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.bitbucket/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on your Bitbucket instance You need to perform the following steps :
 Bitbucket admin privileges A RSA Key Pair  Create a CDS application in BitBucket In Bitbucket go to Administration Settings / Application Links. Create a new Application with :
 Name : CDS Type : Generic Application Application URL : Your CDS URL Display URL : Your CDS URL  On this application, you just have to set up OAuth Incoming Authentication :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gitlab</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager.gitlab/</guid>
      <description>Authorize CDS on your Gitlab instance What you need to perform the following steps :
 Gitlab admin privileges  Create a CDS application on Gitlab In Gitlab go to Settings / Application section. Create a new application with :
 Name : CDS Redirect URI : http(s):///repositories_manager/oauth2/callback  Scopes :
 API read_user read_registry  Connect CDS to Gitlab Using CDS CLI, run :
 $ cds admin reposmanager add GITLAB mygitlab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatcheries</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries/</guid>
      <description>Hatchery is a service dedicated to spawn and kill worker in accordance with build queue needs.
An hatchery is started with permissions to build all pipelines accessible from a given group, using token.
There are 6 modes for hatcheries:
 Local (Start local workers on a single host) Marathon (Start worker model instances on a mesos cluster with marathon framework) Swarm (Start worker on a docker swarm cluster) Openstack (Start virtual machines on an openstack cluster) VSphere (Start virtual machines on an VSphere cluster)  Local mode Hatchery starts workers directly as local process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Swarm</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.swarm/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using Docker Swarm to spawn CDS Worker.
Start Swarm hatchery Generate a token for group:
$ cds generate token -g shared.infra -e persistent fc300aad48242d19e782a37d361dfa3e55868a629e52d7f6825c7ce65a72bf92  Edit the CDS configuration or set the dedicated environment variables. To enable the hactchery, just set the API HTTP and GRPC URL, the token freshly generated.
This hatchery use the standard docker environment variables to connect to a docker host.
Then start hatchery:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker/</guid>
      <description>A pipeline is structured in sequential stages containing one or multiple concurrent jobs. A Job will be executed by a worker.
Building your own worker model enables you to integrate your own tools, or to customize the tools you need to use. For instance, to build an AngularJs application, you shall need a worker capable of installing npm tools, importing bower packages (these are nodeJs tools), building webfonts with fontforge&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker Model</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.worker.model/</guid>
      <description>Purpose The goal of CDS is to start a worker when you need it, which should match all your requirements exactly. In order to scale automatically on demand, it is possible to register a worker model.
The goal of a worker model is to describe the capabilities of a given docker/iso image in terms of architecture, pre-installed binaries or libraries.
Types There are 2 types of worker models:
 Docker images, see how to create a worker model docker Openstack images, see how to create a worker model openstack  Capabilities Capabilities have a name, a type and a value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Openstack</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.openstack/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using Openstack infrastructure to spawn each CDS Workers inside dedicated virtual machine.
Start Opentack hatchery Generate a token for group:
$ cds generate token -g shared.infra -e persistent fc300aad48242d19e782a37d361dfa3e55868a629e52d7f6825c7ce65a72bf92  Edit the CDS configuration or set the dedicated environment variables. To enable the hactchery, just set the API HTTP and GRPC URL, the token freshly generated and the openstack variables.
Then start hatchery:
engine start hatchery:openstack --config config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchery Vsphere</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.vsphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.vsphere/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using VMWare Vsphere infrastructure to spawn each CDS Workers inside dedicated VM.
Pre-requisites This hatchery spawns VM which obtains IP from DHCP. So first you have to create a DHCP server on your host with NAT if you want to access to the internet. In order to create you have multiple possibilities like create your own VM with a DHCP server configured or if you are comfortable with the VMWare tools you can use the NSX system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repositories Manager</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.repositories_manager/</guid>
      <description>CDS can be linked to following repositories manager :
 Atlassian Stash / Bitbucket Github Gitlab  It allows you to enable some CDS features such as :
 Create application in CDS from Bitbucket or Github Attach an application to its Bitbucket or Github repository Fully automatic hook management Branch filtering on application workflows Commit logs on pipeline build details  Go through this tutorial to enable the link between repositories managers and CDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write a Plugin</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.write-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.write-plugin/</guid>
      <description>A CDS worker executes job, and job is composed of steps.
A step is :
 a builtin action, as GitClone, etc&amp;hellip; read more a user action read more a Plugin Action  A Plugin is a Golang Binary.
Take a look at https://github.com/ovh/cds/tree/master/sdk/plugin/dummy/dummy_plugin.go
Contribute on https://github.com/ovh/cds/tree/master/contrib/plugins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write your own hatchery</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.write.hatchery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced.hatcheries.write.hatchery/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contribute to add new Hatchery mode.
See Tutorial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/advanced/advanced/</guid>
      <description> Generate a Token Hatcheries Worker Repositories Manager Write a Plugin  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>