<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Check npm vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_npm_vulnerabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_npm_vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will create a CDS Workflow with the Web UI that check JavaScript vulnerabilities
 Create a workflow using one pipeline You will discover the npm-audit-parser plugin action, which parse npm audit report   1 - Create your CDS project Let&amp;rsquo;s create a project. On the top navbar, click on &amp;lsquo;Create a project&amp;rsquo;.
 Enter a Project Name The project key will be useful when you want to use cdsctl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Init a CDS Workflow from a repository</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/init_workflow_with_cdsctl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/init_workflow_with_cdsctl/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will create a CDS Workflow from an existing git repository.
 This will creates you some files inside your local git repository. Then you&amp;rsquo;ll can push them to get a CDS workflow lives with his configuration &amp;lsquo;as code&amp;rsquo;.   Prerequisites  Have an account on your CDS instance Have a Repository manager as GitHub, Bitbucket Server or GitLab set up on your CDS Instance. Have cdsctl command line, you can download it from here  To get started with CDS  In a terminal, go into your git repository and login with cdsctl  $ cd &amp;lt;path-to-repo&amp;gt; $ cdsctl login -H &amp;lt;cds-api-url&amp;gt; # you will be ask for your username and password  Create your first workflow  $ cdsctl workflow init This will ask you to choose:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Import a CDS Workflow from a repository</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/import_workflow_with_webui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/import_workflow_with_webui/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will create a CDS Workflow from an existing git repository.
 The repository have to add .cds/ directory. With the web UI, on will create a CDS Workflow &amp;lsquo;as code&amp;rsquo;.   Prerequisites  Have an account on your CDS instance Have a Repository manager as GitHub, Bitbucket Server or GitLab set up on your CDS Instance.  Prepare your git repository The easiest way to initialize cds files in your repository is to follow first tutorial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Requirement NGINX</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/service-requirement-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/service-requirement-nginx/</guid>
      <description>Add the service requirement  Name: mynginx. This will be the service hostname Type: service Docker Image: nginx:1.11.1. This is the name of Docker image to link to current job  Add a step of type script Docker image nginx:1.11.1 start a nginx at startup. So, it&amp;rsquo;s now available on http://mynginx
curl -v -X GET http://mynginx Execute Pipeline
See output:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build &amp; Deploy a standard application</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_build_deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_build_deploy/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will create a CDS Workflow with the Web UI.
 Create a workflow using two pipelines: one for building, another for deploying Discover application and environments concepts. Discover Run Conditions.   This tutorial seems very long, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, it&amp;rsquo;s very detailed and it will take you about 10-15 minutes to try it.
You will play with many CDS Concepts, discover the reuse of pipelines, how to play with CDS Variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Requirement PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/service-requirement-pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/service-requirement-pg/</guid>
      <description>Add the service requirement Requirement Service
 Type: service Hostname: mypg. This will be the service hostname Docker Image: postgres:9.5.3. This is the name of Docker image to link to current job Options:  POSTGRES_USER=myuser POSTGRES_PASSWORD=mypassword And a requirement model which allow you to execute apt-get install -y postgresql-client, see HowTo
Add a step of type script Docker image postgres:9.5.3 start a PostgreSQL at startup. So, it&amp;rsquo;s now available on mypg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build, tag and release an application</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_build_tag_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/step_by_step_build_tag_release/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will create a CDS Workflow with the Web UI.
 Create a workflow using two pipelines: one for building, a second for tagging You will discover the GitTag action, which create tag compatible which Semantic Verstionning 2.0.0   1 - Create your CDS project Let&amp;rsquo;s create a project. On the top navbar, click on &amp;lsquo;Create a project&amp;rsquo;.
 Enter a Project Name The project key will be useful when you want to use cdsctl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker Model OpenStack</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/worker_model-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/worker_model-openstack/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using OVH.com OpenStack infrastructure
Create OpenStack user In OVH manager, in cloud section, click on the menu on the Servers&amp;gt;OpenStack item.
You will be able to create a worker model OpenStack user, enter description (name and password will be generated).
Add OpenStack worker model We need to define an OpenStack worker model to have OpenStack hatchery booting workers.
We will create a model called testopenstack:
 With low hardware capacity (vps-ssd-1) On Debian 8 With Docker ready to use Git installed  You need to configure:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worker Model vSphere</title>
      <link>/docs/tutorials/worker_model-vsphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/tutorials/worker_model-vsphere/</guid>
      <description>CDS build using vSphere infrastructure
Add vSphere worker model We need to define a vSphere worker model to have vSphere hatchery booting workers.
We will create a worker model called debian8-docker:
 On Debian 8 With Docker ready to use Git installed  You need to configure:
 The image is the name of your virtual machine that you have created before on your host to clone (See Advanced) Pattern If you aren&amp;rsquo;t an administrator you have to choose a configuration pattern in order to fill pre command, worker command and post command with a pattern that an administrator have already fill for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
