<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitLab on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/integrations/gitlab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitLab on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/integrations/gitlab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Authentication</title>
      <link>/docs/integrations/gitlab/gitlab_authentication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/integrations/gitlab/gitlab_authentication/</guid>
      <description>The GitHub Authentication Integration have to be configured on your CDS by a CDS Administrator.
This integration allows you to authenticate user with the GitHub Authentication.
Resume on what you have to do before using the GitHub Authentication Integration  As a CDS Administrator: Create a CDS application on GitLab Complete CDS Configuration File  How to configure GitLab integration What you need to perform the following steps:
 GitLab admin privileges  Create a CDS application on GitLab Notice: if you have already a CDS Application in GitLab for Repository Manager, you can&amp;rsquo;t reuse it for Authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Repository Manager</title>
      <link>/docs/integrations/gitlab/gitlab_repository_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/integrations/gitlab/gitlab_repository_manager/</guid>
      <description>The GitLab Repository Manager Integration have to be configured on your CDS by a CDS Administrator.
This integration allows you to link a Git Repository hosted by GitLab to a CDS Application.
This integration enables some features:
 Git Repository Webhook Easy to use action CheckoutApplication and GitClone for advanced usage Send build notifications on your Pull-Requests and Commits on GitLab. More information  How to configure GitLab integration What you need to perform the following steps:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
