<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>database on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/</link>
    <description>Recent content in database on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database delete Delete a database migration from table gorp_migration (use with caution)
Synopsis Delete a database migration from table gorp_migration (use with caution)
cdsctl admin database delete SERVICE ID Examples  $ cdsctl admin database delete api id-migration-to-delete $ cdsctl admin database delete cdn id-migration-to-delete Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database list List all CDS DB migrations
Synopsis List all CDS DB migrations
cdsctl admin database list SERVICE [flags] Examples  $ cdsctl admin database list api $ cdsctl admin database list cdn Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list-encrypted-data</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list-encrypted-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list-encrypted-data/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database list-encrypted-data List all encrypted data in database
Synopsis List all encrypted data in database
cdsctl admin database list-encrypted-data SERVICE Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl admin database	- Manage CDS Database  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list-signed-data</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list-signed-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/list-signed-data/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database list-signed-data List all signed data in database
Synopsis List all signed data in database
cdsctl admin database list-signed-data SERVICE [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --format string Output format: plain|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;plain&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roll-encrypted-data</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/roll-encrypted-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/roll-encrypted-data/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database roll-encrypted-data Roll a encrypted data in database
Synopsis Roll a encrypted data in database
cdsctl admin database roll-encrypted-data SERVICE ENTITY ... [flags] Options  --index string Resume from a specific index (only available for one entity) Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roll-signed-data</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/roll-signed-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/roll-signed-data/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database roll-signed-data Roll a signed data in database
Synopsis Roll a signed data in database
cdsctl admin database roll-signed-data SERVICE ENTITY ... [flags] Options  --index string Resume from a specific index (only available for one entity) Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unlock</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/unlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/admin/database/unlock/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl admin database unlock Unlock a pending migration (Use with caution)
Synopsis Unlock a pending migration (Use with caution)
cdsctl admin database unlock SERVICE ID Examples  $ cdsctl admin database unlock api id-to-unlock $ cdsctl admin database unlock cdn id-to-unlock Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
