<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>consumer on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in consumer on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl consumer delete Delete an auth consumer
Synopsis Delete an auth consumer
cdsctl consumer delete CONSUMER-ID [USERNAME] Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl consumer	- Manage CDS auth consumers  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl consumer list List your auth consumers for given user
Synopsis List your auth consumers for given user
cdsctl consumer list [USERNAME] [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -g, --group strings filter by group -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key --verbose Display all object fields Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/new/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/new/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl consumer new Create a new auth consumer for current user
Synopsis Create a new auth consumer for current user
cdsctl consumer new [USERNAME] [flags] Options  --description string What is the purpose of this consumer --duration string Validity period of the token generated for the consumer (in days) --groups strings Define the list of groups for the consumer --name string What is the name of this consumer --scopes strings Define the list of scopes for the consumer --service-name string Name of the service --service-region string Region where the service will be started --service-type string Type of service (hatchery, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>regen</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/regen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/consumer/regen/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl consumer regen Regenerate an existing auth consumer
Synopsis Regenerate an existing auth consumer
cdsctl consumer regen CONSUMER-ID [USERNAME] [flags] Options  --duration string Validity period of the token generated for the consumer (in days) --overlap string Overlap duration between actual token and the new one. eg: 24h, 30m Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
