<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vcs on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vcs on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl project vcs delete Delete a VCS configuration on a project
Synopsis Delete a VCS configuration on a project
cdsctl project vcs delete [ PROJECT-KEY ] NAME [flags] Options  --force Force delete without confirmation and exit 0 if resource does not exist Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>export</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/export/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl project vcs export Export a VCS configuration from a project to stdout
Synopsis Export a VCS configuration from a project to stdout
cdsctl project vcs export [ PROJECT-KEY ] NAME Examples cdsctl vcs export MY-PROJECT MY-VCS-SERVER-NAME &amp;gt; file.yaml Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>import</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/import/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/import/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl project vcs import Import a VCS configuration on a project from a yaml file
Synopsis Import a VCS configuration on a project from a yaml file
cdsctl project vcs import [ PROJECT-KEY ] FILENAME [flags] Examples cdsctl project vcs import MY-PROJECT file.yml Options  --force Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/project/vcs/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl project vcs list List VCS available on a project
Synopsis List VCS available on a project
cdsctl project vcs list [ PROJECT-KEY ] [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key --verbose Display all object fields Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
