<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker Compose on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker Compose on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose</title>
      <link>/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/docker-compose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/docker-compose/</guid>
      <description>Run with Docker-Compose This tutorial allows you to start a CDS locally quickly.
 Do not use this docker-compose installation to run it in production without modification. For production purpose, please read CDS Services   The docker-compose.yml contains:
 cds-db service with a PostgreSQL cds-cache service with a Redis elasticsearch service with an Elasticsearch dockerhost allows cds-hatchery-swarm service to communicate with the local docker daemon cds-migrate service to prepare databases for API and CDN cds-api service cds-ui service cds-elasticsearch service cds-hatchery-swarm service cds-vcs service cds-repositories service cds-cdn service  Docker compose is very convenient to launch CDS for testing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Compose Full Tutorial</title>
      <link>/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/full-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hosting/ready-to-run/docker-compose/full-example/</guid>
      <description>Run with Docker-Compose - Full Tutorial This page will help you to create a public instance of CDS:
 installed on a Virtual Machine with a Public Cloud Instance on Openstack with a domain name and SSL configured installed with docker-compose  The whole tutorial of docker-compose is duplicated here. This article contains additional details on HAPRoxy, SSL configuration, IP Restriction.
At the end of this tutorial, you will have a CDS running with all CDS Services and a Swarm Hatchery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
