<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>repository on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/</link>
    <description>Recent content in repository on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>add</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/add/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/add/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl experimental project repository add Add a repository on the project
Synopsis Add a repository on the project
cdsctl experimental project repository add [ PROJECT-KEY ] VCS-NAME REPOSITORY-NAME Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -n, --no-interactive Set to disable interaction with ctl --verbose Enable verbose output SEE ALSO  cdsctl experimental project repository	- Manage repositories on a CDS project  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl experimental project repository delete Remove a repository from on a project
Synopsis Remove a repository from on a project
cdsctl experimental project repository delete [ PROJECT-KEY ] VCS-NAME REPOSITORY-NAME [flags] Options  --force Force delete without confirmation and exit 0 if resource does not exist Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hook-key</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/hook-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/hook-key/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl experimental project repository hook-key Get repository webhook secret key
Synopsis Get repository webhook secret key
cdsctl experimental project repository hook-key [ PROJECT-KEY ] VCS-TYPE VCS-NAME REPOSITORY-NAME [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --format string Output format: plain|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;plain&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key --verbose Display all object fields Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/components/cdsctl/experimental/project/repository/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl experimental project repository list List available repositories on a project
Synopsis List available repositories on a project
cdsctl experimental project repository list [ PROJECT-KEY ] [flags] Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key --vcs-name string Specified a VCS by its name --verbose Display all object fields Options inherited from parent commands  -c, --context string cdsctl context name -f, --file string set configuration file --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
