<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>user on CDS Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/</link>
    <description>Recent content in user on CDS Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>add</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/add/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/add/</guid>
      <description> cdsctl group user add Add a user into a group
Synopsis Add a user into a group
cdsctl group user add GROUPNAME USERNAME [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for add  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -w, --no-warnings do not display warnings -v, --verbose verbose output  SEE ALSO  cdsctl group user - Manage CDS users group  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/delete/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl group user delete Delete an user from a group
Synopsis Delete an user from a group
cdsctl group user delete GROUPNAME USERNAME [flags]  Options  --force Force delete without confirmation and exit 0 if resource does not exist -h, --help help for delete  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>removeAdmin</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/removeadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/removeadmin/</guid>
      <description> cdsctl group user removeAdmin Remove a user from administrators of a group
Synopsis Remove a user from administrators of a group
cdsctl group user removeAdmin GROUPNAME USERNAME [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for removeAdmin  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -w, --no-warnings do not display warnings -v, --verbose verbose output  SEE ALSO  cdsctl group user - Manage CDS users group  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>setAdmin</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/setadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/group/user/setadmin/</guid>
      <description> cdsctl group user setAdmin Set a user as an administrator of a group
Synopsis Set a user as an administrator of a group
cdsctl group user setAdmin GROUPNAME USERNAME [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for setAdmin  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -w, --no-warnings do not display warnings -v, --verbose verbose output  SEE ALSO  cdsctl group user - Manage CDS users group  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>