<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>keys on CDS Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in keys on CDS Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>add</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/add/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/add/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl application keys add Add a new key on application. key type can be ssh or pgp
Synopsis Add a new key on application. key type can be ssh or pgp
cdsctl application keys add KEY APP-NAME KEY-NAME KEY-TYPE [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for add  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delete</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/delete/</guid>
      <description> cdsctl application keys delete Delete CDS an application key
Synopsis Delete CDS an application key
cdsctl application keys delete KEY APP-NAME KEY-NAME [flags]  Options  -h, --help help for delete  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers. -w, --no-warnings do not display warnings -v, --verbose verbose output  SEE ALSO  cdsctl application keys - Manage CDS application keys  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>list</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/cli/cdsctl/application/keys/list/</guid>
      <description>cdsctl application keys list List CDS application keys
Synopsis List CDS application keys
cdsctl application keys list KEY APP-NAME [flags]  Options  --fields string Only display specified object fields. &#39;empty&#39; will display all fields, &#39;all&#39; will display all object fields, &#39;field1,field2&#39; to select multiple fields --filter string Filter output based on conditions provided --format string Output format: table|json|yaml (default &amp;quot;table&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for list -q, --quiet Only display object&#39;s key  Options inherited from parent commands  -f, --file string set configuration file -k, --insecure (SSL) This option explicitly allows curl to perform &amp;quot;insecure&amp;quot; SSL connections and transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>