<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Requirement on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Requirement on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Access</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_network/</guid>
      <description>The Network Access prerequisite allow you to require a worker to have access to a specific server
Example:
golang.org:80  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Link</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_service/</guid>
      <description>The Service Link prerequisite allow you to use any Docker image as a dependency of a job.
This is pretty useful if you want to make some tests with a real database, or put your builded application as a job prerequisite for doing some tests.
How to use service requirement When editing a pipeline job, choose your model as usual, then add a new service requirement, the name you set will be the service&amp;rsquo;s hostname, set the Docker image for the service as the value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OS &amp; Architecture</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_os_arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_os_arch/</guid>
      <description>The OS-Architecture prerequisite allow you to require a worker with a specific OS &amp;amp; Architecture.
Beware about default value: there is a default value for OS &amp;amp; Architecture, it&amp;rsquo;s specified in CDS API Configuration.
If user does not specify a prerequisite os-architecture, the default value is applied when the job is in CDS Queue.
Then, a hatchery will spawn a worker compiled with the specified os-architecture prerequisite.
Beware about launching job: if you put a prerequisite os-architecture with value linux/386, the job won&amp;rsquo;t be launched by a worker linux/amd64 even if technically speaking, the worker could launch this job without issue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>