<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Requirement on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Requirement on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/docs/concepts/requirement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Region Requirement</title>
      <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_region/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_region/</guid>
      <description>The Region prerequisite allows you to require a worker to have access to a specific region.
A Region can be configured on each hatchery. With a free text as myregion in hatchery configuration, user can set a prerequisite &amp;lsquo;region&amp;rsquo; with value myregion on CDS Job.
Example of job configuration:
jobs: - job: build requirements: - region: myregion steps: ... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Requirement</title>
      <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_secret/</guid>
      <description>The Secret prerequisite allows you to require a worker to start with some project&amp;rsquo;s secrets when those secrets are not automatically injected.
Secret automatic injection can be disabled if a job requires to run in a specific region (using a &amp;ldquo;Region&amp;rdquo; prerequisite) that was added in CDS API configuration (key: skipProjectSecretsOnRegion).
The value for the requirement should be a valid regex. In the following example it is used to match both default SSH and PGP keys for a CDS project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Link</title>
      <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_service/</guid>
      <description>The Service Link prerequisite allow you to use any Docker image as a dependency of a job.
This is useful when you want to make some tests with a real database, or put your built application as a job prerequisite for doing some tests.
How to use service requirement When editing a pipeline job, choose your model as usual, then add a new service requirement (the name you set will be the service&amp;rsquo;s hostname) and set the Docker image for the service as the value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory</title>
      <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_memory/</guid>
      <description>The Memory requirement allows you to require a worker to have a specific number of MiB of RAM.
For example if you need 2 GiB of RAM for your worker you can put 2048 in your memory requirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OS &amp; Architecture</title>
      <link>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_os_arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/concepts/requirement/requirement_os_arch/</guid>
      <description>The OS-Architecture prerequisite allow you to require a worker with a specific OS &amp;amp; Architecture.
Beware about default value: there is a default value for OS &amp;amp; Architecture, it&amp;rsquo;s specified in CDS API Configuration.
If user does not specify a prerequisite os-architecture, the default value is applied when the job is in CDS Queue.
Then, a hatchery will spawn a worker compiled with the specified os-architecture prerequisite.
Beware about launching job: if you put a prerequisite os-architecture with value linux/386, the job won&amp;rsquo;t be launched by a worker linux/amd64 even if technically speaking, the worker could launch this job without issue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
