<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hooks on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</title>
    <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hooks on CDS - Continuous Delivery Service</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Webhook</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/webhook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/webhook/</guid>
      <description>On a Root Pipeline, you can add a &amp;ldquo;Webhook&amp;rdquo;. Click on the created icon to get the WebHook URL.
In order to trigger this one you just have to make a HTTP call on the given URL with the selected method. If the selected method is POST you can also send a payload from your workflow inside the request body or if you use GET method you can write your payload using query parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/scheduler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/scheduler/</guid>
      <description>On a Root Pipeline, you can add a &amp;ldquo;Hook Scheduler&amp;rdquo;. This kind of hook is useful when you want to launch a workflow periodically (for example each day at 1AM). You can use the Crontab Expression Format to configure your scheduler&amp;rsquo;s period. You can also configure a specific payload for your scheduler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Repository Webhook</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/git-repo-webhook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/git-repo-webhook/</guid>
      <description>You want to run a workflow after a git push on a repository? This kind of hook is for you.
You have to:
 link your project to a Repository Manager, on Advanced Section link an application to a git repository add a Repository Webhook on the root pipeline, this pipeline have the application linked in the context  GitHub / Github Enterprise / Bitbucket Cloud / Bitbucket Server / GitLab are supported by CDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Repository Poller</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/git-repo-poller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/git-repo-poller/</guid>
      <description>You want to run a workflow after a git push on a repository BUT your CDS instance isn&amp;rsquo;t accessible from the internet? This kind of hook is for you. (If your CDS instance is accessible from the internet please check the Git Repository Webhook).
This kind of hook will poll periodically the GitHub API to know the push and pull-request events on your repository.
You have to:
 link your project to a Repository Manager, on Advanced Section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kafka hook</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/kafka-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/kafka-hook/</guid>
      <description>You want to run a workflow from a Kafka message? This kind of hook is for you.
This kind of hook will connect to a Kafka topic and consume message. For each message, it will trigger your workflow.
The Kafka message have to be a JSON message, it in will be used as a payload for your workflow See payload documentation.
Link your project to a Kafka platform On your CDS Project, select the platforms section then add a Kafka platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RabbitMQ hook</title>
      <link>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/rabbitmq-hook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ovh.github.io/cds/docs/concepts/workflow/hooks/rabbitmq-hook/</guid>
      <description>You want to run a workflow from a RabbitMQ message? This kind of hook is for you.
This kind of hook will connect to a RabbitMQ queue and consume message. For each message, it will trigger your workflow.
The RabbitMQ message have to be a JSON message, it in will be used as a payload for your workflow See payload documentation.
Link your project to a RabbitMQ platform On your CDS Project, select the platforms section then add a RabbitMQ platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>